We will now begin the 57th
expedition beyond the walls!
Onward!
The Survey Corps left to find a route to
Zhiganshina, but encountered a Female Titan,
a transformed human like Eren.
That's no Aberrant.
It's a human in the body of a Titan!
As soldiers died, one after the next,
they headed into a
forest of giant trees,
none of them knowing why.
If Squad Levi doesn't
defeat it, who will?
Choose.
Believe in yourself.
Or believe in the Survey Corps and me.
I'll go forward!
Fire!
Oh, right...
I wanted to ask you something.
Is it okay if we cut off
your hands and legs?
They'll grow back, right?
I'm talking about your
limbs, not the Titan's.
We need you alive, after all...
The enemy was willing
to sacrifice everything.
I didn't expect the enemy to destroy
itself along with the evidence
by making Titans devour itself.
Retreat, men!
Back into formation!
Return to Karanes!
Erwin...
Why did you order Levi to resupply?
There's no time to waste.
The Female Titan was eaten.
But did you see the
person inside get eaten?
I didn't.
You can't mean...
Yes...
If your original hypothesis was correct,
and they can still move to a degree
after regaining human form...
And if they'd equipped
Maneuver Gear in advance...
The one within the Female Titan
is wearing our uniform right now.
Captain Levi?
No, it's not!
Who are you?!
Gunther!
The enemy is now camouflaged
as one of our men.
Oh, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
Oh, my friend!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel... We will kill...
The enemy is colossal... We will jump...
In our hands we hold blades of glory
and sing in the name of victory
We bear the wings of freedom on our backs
Swearing iron determination upon our hearts,
we slash apart the circle of idiocy
and soar through the sky
with our wings of freedom
Crushing Blow: The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 5
When the Colossal Titan vanished,
whoever was inside had been
wearing Maneuver Gear,
so that they could escape in the steam.
Don't you think the same
possibility applies here?
But at the time...
Based on what we saw when Eren
emerged from the Titan,
we concluded it would be impossible.
His equipment was destroyed,
and his uniform was gone.
Above all, Eren was so weak,
he couldn't even stand unassisted.
The Female Titan was able to
attract other Titans with its cry.
We failed to predict this,
and the operation failed.
If Titan abilities vary
depending on skill,
it was a mistake to use Eren, a total
novice, as the basis for our assumptions.
If we are to outwit our enemy,
we'll need to think outside the box.
If we're withdrawing, does that
mean the mission succeeded?
If so, then we may already know who
was inside the Female Titan.
I'd like to see who it is...
But why was the Commander so sure
that the enemy would come after
Eren if he left the walls?
I think it's because, for some reason,
they suddenly stopped their advance
in the midst of the last assault.
Even though they managed
to break through Trost's gate,
they didn't even try for the inner gate.
And when Eren sealed
the gate, they let him.
It could mean that they now
have bigger concerns...
Bigger concerns?
Something more important to
them than breaching the walls.
Something unexpected that happened.
Eren's transformation into a Titan?!
I think it's the only answer.
Then... That means...
Wait... So...
Someone who was there,
who saw Eren transform,
is the Titan.
Gunther!
Eren, don't stop!
Onward!
But Gunther...
Who's there?
Protect Eren!
Damn it, what do we do?
Eldo, where should we go?
There isn't time to reach the horses!
Head for HQ, as fast as you can!
Is it from the Female Titan?
Or is there more than one?
Damn you...
How dare you?!
Come at me!
I'll defeat you, even if it kills me!
The Female Titan?
Impossible... Why?
Didn't we catch it?!
If the enemy has some way
to retain its strength,
it may be able to transform once more.
I knew it...
It's coming!
The Female Titan!
Damn you...
How dare you!
This time, I will defeat it!
No!
The three of us will
kill the Female Titan.
You will continue to head
straight for HQ at top speed!
Here's what I have gleaned
from this battle...
If we only focus on
making the best moves,
we will never get the
better of our opponent.
When necessary, we must be
willing to take big risks,
and be prepared to lose everything.
I'll fight, too!
No!
This is the best move...
Your power is too risky!
What? Do you doubt us?
Do you, Eren?
Do you find it that hard to trust us?
Unless we change how we fight,
humanity cannot win!
I believe my squad will be victorious.
Good luck!
We took its sight.
For at least a minute,
it'll be in total darkness!
Kill it during this time!
Screw capturing it...
Kill it now!
Die here without honor!
Make that bitch of a Titan pay!
We won't let your eyes regenerate!
We'll shear off so much muscle
around your shoulders,
you won't be able to keep your arms up!
Shear it off...
Make its arms...
fall!
They're down!
Now the neck!
Shear off the muscles
that support its neck!
And we can strike its weak point!
They're so strong.
The Female Titan is
totally on the defensive.
How can they launch co-op attacks like that
without even speaking to each other?
I bet it's only possible because
they believe in one another.
They've overcome many
hardships that way.
That's why they're so strong,
even right after losing Gunther.
I'll go forward...
If I go forward and believe in them,
without turning back, then...
I'm sure that's the right answer.
I finally understand!
I don't know...
I never have.
I can believe in my own abilities
or the choices of companions I trust.
But no one ever knows
how it will turn out.
Strike the neck, now!
Eldo!
H-How?
It can't possibly see!
It hasn't even been thirty seconds...
Only one eye?
It prioritized one eye
to accelerate the healing...
Is that even possible?
Petra!
We need to regroup!
Petra, now!
Hey...
Die!
How?
My blade can't pierce it...
I...
I will...
I'll kill it!
Eren?
Wait, what? Mikasa?
That voice... Don't tell me...
I made the wrong choice...
I wanted to believe in my companions...
Because of that, everyone died!
If I had believed in myself
from the start and fought...
If I'd only killed it at the beginning!
Back then,
if I'd turned into a Titan...
No...
If I'd fought
even before that...
Captain Levi was there, too.
We would have won.
Maybe we could've captured it.
You aren't wrong.
lf you want to, do it.
I...
I made a choice.
And it killed everyone.
It's my fault they died.
But despite all that...
It's still your fault!
I'll tear you apart...
Once my hand heals,
I'll rip you apart...
Tear you to shreds...
Rip you into tiny pieces...
And eat you!
Eren!
W-Wait... Eren...
Don't go...
Give...
Give Eren back!
Give him back!
Why won't my blade penetrate?
I know that
he's alive...
I know that Eren's alive!
No matter where she goes, I'll kill her,
rip her apart,
and get you out of that filth.
I'm sorry, Eren...
Just wait a little longer...
Wait!
Wh-What are you...
Fall back for now.
Maintain this distance.
It may be tired.
It does not appear to
be going very fast.
He seems to have been bit
right out of the neck.
Is Eren dead?
If we suppose that I am not me,
Can you say with certainty that you are you?
Will you be able to pick up after yourself
Once your sand-like shell breaks and your heart crumbles?
I could hear someone calling
But now my ears are just ringing
It's as if time has frozen
Now, wake up
I began to walk through a deep dark abyss
As swift as a gale, I escaped for my life
I felt like a living corpse
We break out of our walls
To reunite in worlds we've yet to map
"Eren is alive."
"Give Eren back."
The Female Titan took Eren from
Mikasa before her very eyes.
Mikasa joins forces with humanity's
strongest fighter, Levi,
to challenge the Female Titan to battle.
The Defeated: The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 6